officetooltips.com 2019-02-26

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the collection and use of information on our website. Please read this policy before using, or submitting information to, these sites. By using this site, you signify that you agree to this Privacy Policy. Although this site contains links to other websites, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those, or any other, sites. If you have questions about how those websites collect and use data, you should carefully read those sites’ privacy policies. 

## Personal Information Collected on this Website

No personal information is collected on this website from consumers who browse for information.

The only personal information collected on this website is gathered on our "contact us" forms. In the consumer form, fields are provided so that users can submit questions or comments and provide contact information including name, email address, and phone number. We collect this personal information so that we can respond to these inquiries, comments, and questions. We also may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, including by search warrant, subpoena, or court order. 

As discussed below, we also collect non-personally identifiable information on this website. However, we do not merge any of the personal information collected via our contact form with anonymous data collected on our website. 

## Non-Personally Identifiable Data Collected on this Website

We collect and store in server logs non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, IP address, operating system, the date and time of visits, the pages visited on the site, time spent viewing the site, and return visits to the site. We also use Google Analytics, a service that records non-personally identifiable data such as browser type, operating system, the date and time of a visit, where visitors came from, the pages visited on this website, the time spent viewing site, where visitors went when they left the site, and return visits to the site. 

We aggregate this non-personally identifiable data to better understand how visitors use our site, and to help manage, maintain, and report on use of our website. We store IP addresses for fraud detection and prevention purposes. 

We may share this non-personally identifiable data with third parties for the limited purpose of reporting on use of our website, or to comply with applicable law. We also may share this data with our service providers. We do not rent, sell or share any non-personally identifiable data collected on this website with third parties for marketing purposes. 

## Cookies

We use cookies on this website. Cookies are small text files created by a web server, delivered through a web browser, and stored on your computer. They provide a means for websites that you visit to keep track of online patterns and preferences, as well as to identify return visitors. Cookies make the personalization of your web experiences possible, so that you do not need to re-enter your information each time you visit a website. 

You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click “Help” in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly. 

We may allow third-parties, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party’s privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. 

## Third Party Content, Links, and Plug-ins

This site contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those, or any other, sites. If you have questions about how those websites collect and use data, you should carefully read those sites’ privacy policies. 

## NAI/IAB

We are compliant with the policies of several industry groups that focus on effective communication, best practices, and policy review in the field of Online Behavioral Advertising (OBA). These organizations include the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA), and the Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB). We are compliant with both the NAI and DAA self-regulatory codes. We believe that delivering targeted and relevant advertising enhances your internet experience. 

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

As our organization, membership, and services evolve, this Privacy Policy may be revised to reflect those changes. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason. Notice of such amendments will be posted as an updated Privacy Policy on this website, and an effective date will be indicated. Users are encouraged to check our site frequently to review the current Privacy Policy in effect. 

## Questions?

Please [contact us](mailto:support@officetooltips.com) with any questions about this website Privacy Policy.
